人老了  容易伤感
You're getting sentimental in your old age.
是啊
Yeah.
最好来点咖啡
Well, might as well have some coffee.
白痴们
Yo! Idiots!
我可以带小熊吗
Can I carry him?
不行  只能带包里能装下的
No, bud. Only what fits in the bag, all right?
我的零花钱呢
What about my pockets?
都可以带上
All your pockets.
通信
喂
Hello?
我马上就回来  好吗
Bud? I'll be back in a moment, okay?
好的
Okay.
喂  伙计
Hey, bud.
嗯...
So...
你还好吗
You all right?
挺好的
Yeah.
他们叫上了所有派对的小动物
They're calling all the party animals.
耶塔大街922号
922 Yetta Street.
我知道在哪
I know where that is.
好了吗  我们出发
Okay? Here we go.
尾灯匹配所有04年到09年的普锐斯
Yeah, taillight matches any 2004 to 2009 Prius.
什么罪犯会开普锐斯
What kind of criminal drives a Prius?
有社会责任感的
A socially responsible one.
光本市就有一千辆以上  全州七千辆
There's over 1,000 registered in the city, 7,000 in the state.
-有多少在重犯名下  -州里六辆
- How many are registered to felons? - Six in the state.
四个是盗用公款的白领罪犯
Four to embezzlers, white-collar criminals,
一个强奸犯  一个谋杀犯
one to a rapist, one to a murderer.
-从谋杀犯开始  -她被判了无期
- Start with the murderer. - She's in prison for life.
强奸犯在外面
Rapist is out.
找到他
Find him.
来吧
Come on.
-你好  -你好
- Hello. - Hi.
-很高兴见到你  -我也很高兴见到你
- Good to see you. - It's good to see you, too.
-你好  卢克  -这是只小马
- Hi, Luke. - It's a pony.
这种可不容易包装
Those aren't easy to wrap.
你知道派对十一点才开始吧
You know the party is not until 11:00, right?
真的吗
Really?
现在几点  九点左右?
What is it? Around 9:00?
对不起  我应该看得更仔细点的
I'm sorry. I should've read it more carefully.
没关系  去把这个拿给凯莉吧
It's no problem. Why don't you go give this to Carrie?
你可以来帮忙
Well, I guess you can help.
其实我得走了  有点事情要处理
Actually, I've gotta go and run some errands.
对不起
Sorry.
那回头见
We'll see you later then.
多谢你了
Thanks so much.
他有我父母的电话
He has my parents' phone number.
在他外套里  外套上面的兜里
In his jacket. Top pocket of his jacket.
如果我来晚了的话
If I'm running late.
没问题
No problem.
强奸犯坐了轮椅
The rapist is in a wheelchair.
不知道是报应还是纯属倒霉
Not sure if that was karma or just bad luck.
那个谋杀犯  她监禁在哪
The murderer. Where is she incarcerated?
县监狱  就在城里
County, right here in town.
她有丈夫吗  或者能开车的孩子
Does she have a husband or a kid old enough to drive?
怎么了
Yes? What?
劳拉・布伦南的验血结果
Lara Brennan's blood work.
接实验室
Get the lab.
你惹到谁了  肯定的
You pissed somebody off, that's for sure.
还是占线  我接着试
It's still busy. I'll keep trying.
不用了  叫救护车
No. Get an ambulance.
带她去大学医院  在那见面
Take her to University Hospital. I'll meet them there.
好的  谢谢
Right. Thanks.
丈夫  大学老师
Husband, schoolteacher.
家庭地址有吗
You got a home address?
车库是空的  要逮捕证吗
No car in the garage. You want to get a warrant?
要
Yeah.
去办逮捕证
Get the warrant.
劳拉・布伦南被转移到大学医院了
Lara Brennan's being transferred to University Hospital.
-现在吗  -就现在
- Right now? - Right now.
让他们派护卫车
Have them call the escort vehicle.
告诉他们我们十分钟内到医院
Tell them we'll meet them at the hospital in less than 10.
是  我们在  囚犯很安全  没问题
Yeah. Yeah, we're here. Prisoner's secure. No problems.
没问题
Will do.
把手举到我能看见的地方
Hands where I can see 'em.
约翰?
John?
还有电话
And the phone.
你在这干什么  约翰
What are you doing here, John?
把手放在头上
Put your hands on your head.
约翰  你在干什么
John, what are you doing?
松开她  跪下
Uncuff her. Kneel down.
约翰  住手
John, stop this.
跪下  面壁
Kneel down. Face the wall.
2242分队安全
Unit 2242 secure.
-她刚才说...-把警灯放上
- She just said... - Just take the light.
手和脚  系得越紧越好
Hands and feet, pull 'em as tight as you can.
你跟他走出那道门  你们俩就都死定了
You walk out that door with him, you will both be dead.
-闭嘴  -约翰  他是对的
- Shut up. - John, he's right.
听他的  你会让我们都没命的
Listen to him. You're gonna get us killed.
-你为什么这样  -因为我们别无选择
- Why are you doing this? - Because we have no other choice!
-穿上  -不  不是这样的
- Put'em on. - No. That's not true!
-把衣服穿上  劳拉  -不
- Put the clothes on, Lara. - No.
-现在  -不
- Now! - No!
好吧
Okay.
你给儿子打电话告诉他你不能去了
You call your son and tell him you're not coming.
-他在哪  -他在等你
- Where is he? - He's waiting for you.
你想告诉他你不去了吗
You wanna tell him you're not coming?
-你怎么能这样对我  -摁拨号键
- How can you do this to me? - Push "send."
告诉他我也不去了
Tell him I'm not coming, either.
-约翰  -我看起来像要回家吗  劳拉
- John. - Does it look like I'm going home, Lara?
你打给他  告诉他现在他孤零零了
You call him, tell him he's alone now
他爸爸妈妈都不回去了
and his mom and dad are not coming back.
天哪  约翰
Jesus, John.
你个混蛋
You son of a bitch.
我是利弗森医生  有个县监狱来的病人
I'm Dr. Lifson. You've got a patient here from County Jail.
劳拉・布伦南
Lara Brennan?
先静脉注射了50%葡萄糖和二十单位胰岛素
Yes, we started an IV. D50 with 20 units of insulin.
收到
Copy.
保安
Security!
出去  出去
Out! Out!
-喂  -退回去
- Hey, hey. - Back away!
-别犯傻  -待在那别动
- Now don't be stupid. - You stay back!
每个出口都有警察  约翰
We have units at every exit, John.
你想逃的话会被射中的
You will be shot trying to leave.
关门  劳拉
Hit the button, Lara.
-住手  -按下关门键
- Stop. - Hit the button!
约翰  别这样
John, do not do this.
-楼梯在哪  -那边
- Where are the stairs? - There.
一男一女  身穿白大褂  地下
Male and female, white lab coats, parking levels.
会没事的
Hey. It's gonna be okay.
看着我  看着我  一切都会没事的
Look at me, look at me. Everything's gonna be okay.
就按我说的做  一切都会没事的
Just do what I say when I say it. Everything will be okay.
劳拉  把白大褂脱掉
Lara, take the coat off.
来吧
Come on.
好了  你留在这
It's okay. You stay here.
所有保安人员
All security personnel...
-盯着门  -是
- Watch the door! - Yeah.
站住
Stop.
操
Shit.
谁在门厅
Who's in the lobby?
听着  有人在门厅吗
Hey, listen. Is anybody in the lobby?
别看
Don't look.
快跑
Run!
妈的
Great!
回这边来
Back here!
让开
Move.
我们走
Let's get moving!
来吧
Come on.
这边
Here!
前进吧企鹅
Go Penguins!
把头发放下来
Let your hair down.
哈里斯  那边  走
Harris, that way. Go!
喂
Hey!
哈里斯  他们在地铁里  哈里斯  地铁
Harris, they're in the subway. Harris! The subway!
收到
Got it.
他们在站台上
They're on the platform!
把两边车站都封住
Block stations in either directions!
找港务局  停住所有列车
Call the Port Authority. Stop all the trains!
等等  等等
Wait, wait, wait.
我们在干什么
What are we doing?
请离门远一点
Stand clear of the closing doors, please.
让开  匹兹堡警局
Move! Pittsburgh PD!
四号轨道上的列车  让它停下  停下
The train on track four, I want it stopped. Stop that train!
下一站...
Next stop...
抱住我
Hold on to me.
孩子  用两只手扶
Hey, kid, two hands.
不对  不对
No. No.
这边
This way.
那边
There.
-红灯  -扶好
- Red light. - Hold on.
红灯
Red light!
全城警戒  关闭汽车站和火车站
Ring the city. Close bus and train stations.
把他们的外貌特征发到州警察局
And get their description to the state police.
收到
Copy that.
-他们的屁孩子多大  -六岁
- How old is their damn kid? - Six.
找到他
Find out where he is.
-你为什么不告诉我  -你会阻止我的
- Why didn't you tell me? - You would've stopped me.
你的胰岛素在这
Your insulin is in here.
这有个包  刷子  润肤霜  化妆品
There's a case in here. It's got a brush, moisturizer, makeup.
都是以前的  希望我拿对了
Everything you had was old. I hope I got it right.
你记得最后在哪看见他的吗
You remember where you last saw him?
想猜猜看刚刚谁越狱了吗
You want to take a guess who just escaped from jail?
稍等
Hold on a second.
-你好  -你好  我来接我儿子
- Hello. - Hi. I'm here to pick up my son.
他们还没回来呢
They aren't back yet.
从哪回来
Back from where?
从动物园
From the zoo.
这是个动物园派对
It's a zoo party.
他们应该再有一个小时就回来了
They should be back in about an hour
如果你想等的话
if you'd like to wait.
不用了  谢谢你
No. Thank you.
怎么了  怎么回事
What's wrong? What is it?
-他在哪  卢克在哪  -在派对
- Where is he? Where's Luke? - He's at the party.
什么派对  你说派对在这开的
What party? You said the party was here.
我搞错了  她把他们带到动物园去了
I was wrong. She's taken them to the zoo.
动物园
-目的地  匹兹堡动物园  -她谁
- Destination, Pittsburgh Zoo. - She?
预计行驶时间  十七分钟
Estimated drive time, 17 minutes.
凯莉的妈妈  妮可
Carrie's mother, Nicole.
检查附近
Check the neighbors!
我们要找那个男孩
We're looking for the boy
问问这几天街坊们看到的事
and anything they've noticed in the last few days.
剩余时间  十一分钟
Time to destination, 11 minutes.
前方300米  左转
In 1,000 feet, bear left.
前方150米  左转
In 500 feet, bear left.
前方30米  左转
In 100 feet, bear left.
动物园
左转
Bear left.
你转错弯了
You took the wrong turn.
约翰  动物园在后面  你转错了
John, the zoo's behind us. You took the wrong turn.
宝贝  你在干什么
Babe, what are you doing?
她会给我父母打电话的
She'll call my parents.
-什么  -他们会照顾他的
- What? - They'll look after him,
我会找到办法团聚的
and I'll figure out a way of getting him to us.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
我试过了  没时间了
I tried! There's no more time!
现在  我们前面随时会有路障
Any second now, there's gonna be a roadblock ahead of us.
可能现在已经在那了
It might be there now!
如果我们现在不逃  就逃不掉了
If we don't get out now, we don't get out!
我会找到办法和他团聚的  好吗
I'll find a way of getting him to us, all right?
我会找到办法的
I'll find a way.
不用  真的  没事
No, really, it's fine.
你帮忙照顾他  真不知道该怎么谢谢你
I just can't thank you enough for taking care of him.
乐意之至
Hey, it was our pleasure.
我就坐在后面  好吗
I'm going to sit back here, okay?
当然可以
Sure.
请勿驶入
北
洲际公路79
车辆从收费站处滞留
The traffic is backing up at the toll plazas.
城里情况更糟
It's worse downtown
警察封住了火车站
where police have cordoned off the train station
正在搜查所有乘客
and are searching all passengers.
到联盟车站加入我们吧
Joining us from Union Station,
西尔维亚帕特森发来报道
our very own Sylvia Patterson.
约翰
John?
我们怎么办
What are we gonna do?
我们去火车站
We're going to the train station.
-在车里等我  -好
- Stay in the car. - Okay.
先生  十分抱歉市长行程被耽搁了
Sir, I'm sorry the mayor was delayed,
但我没让他们拦下所有车
but I did not tell them to stop every vehicle.
只拦一对夫妇带着个孩子的
Just the ones with a couple and a child.
先生  我知道我...
Sir, I know my...
是  先生
Yes, sir.
你确定只要二十块吗
Are you sure $20 is enough?
到水牛城的票价是这三倍
Ticket to Buffalo costs three times that.
没错  反正我们也要去那
Yeah. We're going that way anyway.
停车收费
扩大范围  把他们的照片发到
Go wider. Send their photos to every
五百公里内所有火车站  汽车站和机场
train, bus station and airport in a 300-mile radius.
那就是俄亥俄  马里兰  西弗吉尼亚
So Ohio, Maryland, West Virginia,
纽约  新泽西  弗吉尼亚
New York, New Jersey, Virginia,
密西根  肯塔基和印第安纳州
Michigan, Kentucky and Indiana?
你知道他们去哪个方向了吗  机灵鬼
You know what direction they're going in, smart-ass?
水牛城
-再见  汤姆  -再次谢谢
- See you again, Tom. - Thanks again.
你想看看吗
You want to see it?
除非它能告诉我他们在哪
Only if it will tell me where they are.
没这么走运
Not so lucky.
加拿大
不好意思  你觉得这能算咖啡吗
Excuse me. Do you call this coffee?
安大略和魁北克有多少机场
How many airports in Ontario and Quebec?
你想让我停下来数数吗
You want me to stop calling and count?
-这么远距离只有随身行李吗  -什么
- Long way to go with just a carry-on. - I'm sorry?
这么远的距离只有随身行李
Long way to go with just a carry-on.
知不知道你们多少次弄丢行李了
You know how many times you guys have lost our bags?
你们的票和登机牌
Here's your tickets and boarding passes.
谢谢
Thank you.
找到他父母了
They found the parents.
你们开了一整天车?
You decided to go for a drive for the entire day?
乔治想看看树叶
George wanted to see the leaves.
你完全不知道他们去哪了  是吗
And you have absolutely no idea where they're going, right?
告诉过你了  我们都不说话
I told you. We never spoke.
我来
I'll do this.
往前走  卢克
Go ahead, Luke.
你好
Hello.
你看起来需要休息
You look like you need to get away.
谢谢
Thank you.
来吧伙计
Come on, buddy.
-没找到更多的  太糟糕了  -是啊
- Too bad you didn't find more of it. - Yeah.
真希望我能想出来这是哪
And I wish I could figure out where this is.
我在网上查了能想到的所有旅游景点
I checked Web sites for every tourist destination I could think of.
-这是总统府  -什么
- That's the Presidential Palace. - What?
地震塌了的时候  电视上全是
It was all over CNN when it collapsed during the earthquake.
我们知道他们要去哪了
We know where they're going!
给我看看
Show me.
谢谢您的等待  我们马上开始排队登机
Thank you for waiting. We'll soon begin boarding by rows.
警报
到门口拦住他们  看看这个
Hold them at the gate. Take a look.
我们走
Let's go!
让一让  大家  不能再登机了
Excuse me, folks. No one else on.
让一让  让一让  请让一让
Excuse me, folks. Excuse me. Excuse me, please.
对不起  这架飞机上没有那样的人
Sorry. There's no one by that description on this flight.
不对  他们在上面
No. They're on it.
你有照片吗
Do you have the photographs?
我们有照片  他们不在这架飞机上
We have the photographs. They're not on this plane.
今晚还有到海地的航班吗
Are there any other flights to Haiti tonight?
没有其它航班了  还有事吗
No other flights. Anything else?
没  没了  谢谢
No. No. Thank you.
开始下雨了
It's starting to rain.
我去给联邦调查局打电话
I'll call the FBI.
你有没有想过为什么我们找到了这个袋子
You ever ask yourself why we found this bag
却没找到其它的
and not the others?
机长关闭了安全带指示灯
The captain has switched off the seat belt light.
今晚飞往委内瑞拉加拉加斯的航班
Flight time to Caracas, Venezuela this evening
飞行时间为五小时三十二分
is five hours and 32 minutes.
在座位上时
While in your seat,
机长请求您系好安全带
the captain asks that you keep your seat belt fastened.
这人是个老师?
This guy's a teacher?
在社区大学
At a community college.
世界地图集
委内瑞拉
-她听到有扣子掉了  -什么
- She heard a button pop. - What?
她听到有扣子掉了
She heard a button pop.
我们搜查现场的时候下雨了吗
Was it raining when we searched the scene?
三年以前?
Three years ago?
我们现在在干嘛
What are we doing here?
专业一点好不好  抓住另一边
Why don't you act like a cop? Grab the other side.
你已经疯了
You're out of your mind.
-准备好了吗  -好了
- Ready? - Yeah.
扶稳了吗
You got it?
你真以为能找得到?
You really thought you were gonna find it?